Chittari Hari Vamsi (1) Featured

Sr. Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Asp. NetA, do. Net, MVC, Web API, SQL, C#, Asp. NET Core, Azure, Java Script, Jquery, Git



Current Designation: Senior Software Engineer -Dot Net Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Current Company: Starmark Software Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: M.Tech [Computers]

Pref. Location: Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Sr. Software Engineer, Tech Lead, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Asp. Net, Ado. Net, MVC, Web

API,SQL,C#,Asp.NET Core,Azure,JavaScript,Jquery,Git

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Over 5+ years of experience in Software Development in C#.NET platform. Developing web applications without compromising important key factors of Accessibility and Usability. Which have been depicted at Wireframe stages by using the well-known tools Glt, Visual Studio with MSSQL as database.

Work Experience

Starmark Software as Senior Software Engineer -Dot Net Jan 2018 to Till Date

- ? Handled requirements.
- ? Git repository for version-control system for tracking changes in source code during development of the project.
- ? Programming the functionality of the project using C# language.
- ? Created Web Services for the project.
- ? Designed web page based user interface using ASP.NET controls, HTML and CSS.
- ? Scripting language JavaScript and JQuery for client side.
- ? Created database structure like tables and stored procedures and functions required for the project using SQL Server.

Scientific Games as Software Engineer

Dec 2016 to Jun 2017

- * Developing RDLC Reports.
- * Programming the functionality of the project using C# language.
- * Created database structure like tables and stored procedures required for the project using SQL Server 2016.

Hire Craft as Software Engineer

Jun 2016 to Oct 2016

- * Programming the functionality of the project using C# (Web API).
- * Created database structure like tables and stored procedures and functions required for the project using SQL Server.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from GITAM Institute of International Business, Visakhapatnam in 2014

PG: M.Tech (Computers) in 0

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
GIT			
ASP.NET			
ADO.NET			
MVC			
Web API			
SQL			
C#			
ASP.NET Core			
AZURE			
JavaScript			
JQUERY			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time